{"data":{"questions":[{"correct_answer":"Tell your parents and contact the site administrator.","option_1":"Show it to your friends","option_2":"Ignore it","option_3":"Show it to your friends","option_4":"Tell your parents and contact the site administrator.","question":"If someone creates a social-networking page (such as Facebook or My Space) in your name you should"},{"correct_answer":"Both A and B","option_1":"Leave the site","option_2":"Tell an adult","option_3":"Click on another part, maybe it will be better","option_4":"Both a and b","question":"If a website makes you feel uncomfortable you should"},{"correct_answer":"Flaming (sending hurtful or mean messages)","option_1":"Flaming (sending hurtful or mean messages)","option_2":"Trick or treat","option_3":"Email","option_4":"All of the above","question":"Which of the following is a form of cyberbullying?"},{"correct_answer":"Tell or show it to a teacher or a parent","option_1":"Ignore it","option_2":"Tell or show it to a teacher or a parent","option_3":"Respond to the message","option_4":"Call 999","question":"If a message that is posted on-line is mean or negative in any way, or makes you feel uncomfortable you should"},{"correct_answer":"Screen name","option_1":"Screen name","option_2":"School name and location","option_3":"Your real first name and last name","option_4":"Your phone number and address","question":"What information is okay to use on the internet?"},{"correct_answer":"Cyberbullying","option_1":"Cyberbullying","option_2":"Email","option_3":"Nice","option_4":"Feedback","question":"Harassment through the Internet that is rude and/or threatening is"},{"correct_answer":"Tell a teacher and change your password","option_1":"Ignore it","option_2":"Contact the police","option_3":"Tell a teacher and change your password","option_4":"Find out who gave out your password","question":"If someone steals your password at school you should"},{"correct_answer":"Save and show the messages to a parent, guardian or trusted adult","option_1":"Respond to the message and tell the person what you think","option_2":"Save and show the messages to a parent, guardian or trusted adult","option_3":"Just ignore the messages","option_4":"Delete and ignore the messages","question":"When you get a rude or hurtful message on the computer you should"},{"correct_answer":"All of the above","option_1":"Your email or other personal sites could be tampered with","option_2":"Someone could steal your identity online","option_3":"Your banking or shopping sites could be tampered with by someone you don't know","option_4":"All of the above","question":"Giving your password to a friend could result in the following incidents:"},{"correct_answer":"Ask your parent/teacher permission to use the site.","option_1":"Click okay. Your parents/teachers won't mind.","option_2":"Ask your parent/teacher permission to use the site.","option_3":"Ask your friend for permission","option_4":"None of the above","question":"If a website asks for your parent's permission before you can use it, you should"},{"correct_answer":"Never","option_1":"Never","option_2":"If your online friend wants to meet you in a public place","option_3":"When your best friend has given out his/her information and nothing bad has happened","option_4":"If you have been chatting with a friend online for several weeks and know that person well","question":"It is all right to give out personal information online in the following instances:"}]}}
